Thank you for watching!
Now it's time for the ending.
Please let us hear from Ms. Kokubo.
Yes. Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku Spring Tour 2023 100% Ebism is now underway.
We will be touring all over Japan until July 16th at the Pacifico Yokohama National Grand Hall,
Please come and see us, some venues may still be selling tickets.
Well, that's all for now,
Do you have any memorable monsters?
I mean, do you have any memories of monsters?
I'm from Aichi Prefecture.
I'm from Aichi, so... the places I used to go...
Oh, really?
I was able to perform next to a place where I used to hang out a lot.
I remember it very well.
What kind of monster was it?
It's called the Aichi Arts Center Main Hall.
The Great Hall of Aichi Arts Center.
Yes, it's right next door to Oasis 21.
It's going to open next to Oasis 21.
I used to go there instead of school.
I see. So you went to the middle of the hall or the middle of the hall.
I used to go to the middle of the hall.
That's where I used to go.
Did your local friends come too?
Yes, they came.
My friend said she didn't know much about Ebbetson's music, but she really enjoyed the show.
He said he really enjoyed it and asked me for the set list.
Please give me the setlist.
I'm glad to hear that you've heard so many of my songs.
I'm so happy, I'm so happy!
Now we're going to go to many more places, including Hokkaido and Okinawa, starting from Hokkaido in the north.
I've already been all over the country for this job, haven't I? I was able to do a lot of traveling on last year's spring tour, and this year is the first time I'll be performing in Okinawa.
This is the first time we're performing in Okinawa this year, so we're really looking forward to it.
We're looking forward to it. We're going to have a great live show and we'll have 5 minutes.
Well, we may have time to go visit Okinawa.
I'm so glad.
I'm going to go there.
I hope you are looking forward to it, too!
And now...
On August 5th and 6th at Kirara Theater Hibiki, Lake Yamanaka Koryu Plaza
We are going to hold "EBICHU Summer Family Productions: FAMIE IN YAMANAKAKO 2023" at Kirara Theater Hibiki in Lake Yamanaka Koryu Plaza on August 5th and 6th.
It's an annual event!
How many times have you been to this event, Mr. Fukuoka? This is my second time.
This is my second time.
Second time?
You mean last year was your first?
The year before last, I couldn't make it because of Corona.
So you didn't do it the year before.
I see what you mean.
What do you think? There's lots of water and water cannons.
It's so much fun.
It's like a summer event.
I think it's going to be a lot of fun.
I think it will be a lot of fun.
It's the first time Emma Ender is participating in this year's Famiye, so...
I guess so. But it's a great venue, isn't it?
I'm really looking forward to performing in the mountains with a sense of openness.
I hope you're looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Last but not least, Ms. Kunitomo.
I'd like to give you a present of tea that will cheer you up when you pass by at night.
Oh! Thank you very much.
Today's tea is jasmine tea.
Wow! Thank you very much.
Refreshing aroma in your mouth.
It's spreading in my mouth.
It smells so good!
Bon appétit!
How is it?
Oh, it's delicious!
Oh! Good! Want some tea? Are you from Nagoya?
Yes, I do! I especially like jasmine tea.
Oh!
I drink jasmine tea at lessons, too.
Is that so?
Yes, I do!
It's so good!
I learned a lot of things today.
But when I make gummy bears, I use lactobacillus acidophilus and many other things.
But it looks delicious even if you make it with tea.
Really? Tea gummies?
But if it's jasmine tea gummies...
Please experiment a little.
I'll try.
Report back to me, all of you.
Good, good, good! Jasmine tea, sir!
Well! How are you doing this time, Mr. Koko? After talking to you...
I was not as nervous as I thought I would be.
I'm glad we talked a lot.
Really?
Yes!
I'm glad. I'm glad.
Thank you very much.
Now then, may I ask you for a few closing words?
May I have your closing words?
Please come to our concerts. We'll be waiting for you.
That was Kokuboyno. Bye bye.
Bye-bye.
This program is Jimmy.
Mr. Hiromaru.Mr. Hiromaru
Mr. Fan from Chair
Mr. Ryokichi
Sent to you courtesy of Maiki-san
Thank you very much.